{
    "id": "ff75b5953e2445159d34fb97d6aa4849",
    "title": "Conjunctions Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "………………………. we leave now, we will miss the bus home.",
            "description": "Unless expresses a condition. It is similar to if...not....",
            "answers": [
                "If",
                "Without",
                "Unless"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "37008a4c550e4169a54a90b95910ac41"
        },
        {
            "question": "………………………. you like it or not, you are not wearing that skirt to school.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "If",
                "Whether",
                "Unless"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "53031cefa97f4349a94a989c673863a3"
        },
        {
            "question": "…………………………. he didn’t want me to know the truth, I found out any way.",
            "description": "Although is used to connect two contrasting ideas. ",
            "answers": [
                "Although",
                "However",
                "If"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "f80f861d9135482896a06ec5a503d05e"
        },
        {
            "question": "I couldn’t enjoy the outing ………………………. it was too cold.",
            "description": "Because shows the reason.",
            "answers": [
                "because",
                "so",
                "though"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "1987a73ff92f4343b5794039833d68b4"
        },
        {
            "question": "………………………… he had bet on the wrong horse, he lost a lot of money.",
            "description": "Either as or since can be used here.",
            "answers": [
                "Since",
                "If",
                "As"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "19c466ebbbb64097addb63bbf8849c1a"
        },
        {
            "question": "He couldn’t buy the ring ………………………….. he didn’t have enough money.",
            "description": "Because shows the reason.",
            "answers": [
                "because",
                "so",
                "however"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "b4e6f910a12d4fbea74b4f52448b0a4b"
        },
        {
            "question": "The streets were wet ………………………….. it rained last night.",
            "description": "Either for or because can be used here. ",
            "answers": [
                "for",
                "because",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "09f64a683a614dbaa008ac491e1b10b7"
        },
        {
            "question": "……………………….. you are late to bed, you will feel sleepy in the morning.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "If",
                "Unless",
                "Whether"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "316c9acaec404eafaa24b704a8706720"
        },
        {
            "question": "………………………… you leave office a little early today, we cannot go to movies.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Unless",
                "If",
                "Whether"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "3e28db3aa45d4e6f8d8067e2e8f76e5d"
        },
        {
            "question": "………………………… I were you, I would not go there all alone.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "If",
                "Unless",
                "Whether"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "575ae833c42e436191ba8597c83147c9"
        },
        {
            "question": "…………………….. she was not there, I spoke to her mother.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "As",
                "If",
                "Though"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "a6fabd9e6004448ebc93ad2acd7dab75"
        },
        {
            "question": "He finished first ……………………….. he started late.",
            "description": "Either though or although is possible here. ",
            "answers": [
                "although",
                "as",
                "though"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "9dadabef25f24a63bb58891c900d6781"
        }
    ]
}